https://thefallongroup.com/privacy-policy/

» Privacy Policy
The Fallon Group – Online Loans
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The following disclosure pertains to the use of our website. Please note, the operators of this website (TheFallonGroup.com) are working strictly under an advertising capacity and may receive compensation as an affiliate from the loan offers and advertisement offers for peer to peer lending and online personal loan and offers identified online. The operators do not host forms or consumer applications on their personal web servers.
Information Collection and Use
TheFallonGroup.com the owner of this website, in conjunction with its affiliate partners and advertisers, collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. Information collected on this site may be used for analysis purposes, mostly on an aggregate level.
Privacy Notice
TheFallonGroup.com recognizes that protecting the privacy and security of the personal information we obtain about our customers is an important responsibility. This Privacy Notice generally describes our policy about how we treat that information. This notice refers TheFallonGroup.com using the terms “we,” “us,” and “our.”
How we obtain information:
We obtain most of the information we need directly from you on your application or other forms you complete, or from those you have authorized to provide information to us in connection with providing our services to you. We also obtain information in the course of processing and recording your transactions with us.
Information we may obtain:
The type of information we obtain depends on the type of product or service in which you express interest. The types of information we may obtain fall into the following two general categories:
– Customer Information. Customer information includes identifying information such as your name, address, telephone number, and demographic data about you.
– Financial Information. Financial information is information covered by the Fair Credit Reporting Act and includes information such as your credit history, income, assets.
Security of the information:
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with Federal and State laws to protect all the information we have obtained about you.
What we do with the information we obtain:
We use information about you for business purposes such as identifying the products and services which will meet your needs and for processing your applications.
Disclosure of information:
Please note, we do not host applications or forms on our servers that collect personal consumer information. Our partner and financial or loan affiliate partners, may in order to offer you products and services that may be of value to you, we may, where permitted by law, disclose the customer information described above to the following anyone to whom you have authorized us to disclose the information; – others as permitted* or required by law.
Third Party Cookies and Session IDs:
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies and session IDs by TheFallonGroup.com commonly and does not cover the use of cookies and session IDs by any advertisers, sponsors or partner/linked sites.
Sharing:
Legal Disclaimer: Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Links to other websites:
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TheFallonGroup.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. Please note that TheFallonGroup.com has financial relationships with some of the merchants mentioned here. may be compensated TheFallonGroup.com if consumers choose to utilize the links located throughout the content on this site and generate sales for the said merchant
Finance News'Bowling Alone' at 20---and Other Books to Read October 9, 2020Nancy Pelosi's Insanity Plea October 9, 2020Democrats introduce a radical bill to remove Presidents.Kamala Harris Gets a Fracking Education October 9, 2020Pence is right: Shale drilling for natural gas has cut C02 emissions.The New England Journal of Politics, Part II October 9, 2020The medical editors prefer China’s virus management.The Captain of Operation Warp Speed October 9, 2020Moncef Slaoui explains how a public-private partnership is overcoming technical and bureaucratic obstacles to find a way of inoculating against Covid.Mike Pence and the GOP Mount a Last Stand in Arizona October 9, 2020Most voters have made up their minds, so the Trump campaign is rallying the conservative ‘old guard.’The Tyranny of the 'Tolerant' October 9, 2020They’ll tear you down if you use the wrong word, have a flawed past, fail to salute the fashionable woke flag.Pelosi Suspects Trump Crazy Enough to Take Her Stimulus Deal October 9, 2020Taxpayers hoping for a reprieve may be disappointed.Why Politicians Despise Us---Continued October 9, 2020Among the fibs at the vice presidential debate, the worst is a bipartisan myth about the virus’s spread.A New Generation Fights for Afghanistan October 9, 2020Ahmad Massoud, 31, commands anti-Taliban fighters 19 years after his legendary father’s assassination.
Recent Posts
1000 to 35,000 Installment Loans Online
Gatesville NC
Unsecured Installment Loans Online In Gates NC
Installment Loans From Direct Lenders In Gastonia NC
Online Installment Loans and Lenders In Gaston North Carolina
Personal Loans and Online Lenders In Garysburg North Carolina
Archives
March 2019
June 2018
April 2018
March 2018
September 2017
July 2016
July 2015
Kingdom City MO
LEGAL DISCLAIMER: THIS WEBSITE DOES NOT CONSTITUTE AN OFFER OR SOLICITATION TO LEND. THEFALLONGROUP.COM IS NOT A LENDER AND DOES NOT MAKE LOANS OR CREDIT DECISIONS. THEFALLONGROUP.COM PROVIDES A MATCHING SERVICE ONLY AND IS NOT ACTING AS A REPRESENTATIVE, AGENT, OR CORRESPONDENT FOR ANY OF THE LENDERS WE CONTRACT WITH. THEFALLONGROUP.COM DOES NOT CHARGE A SERVICE FEE. THEFALLONGROUP.COM DOES NOT CONTROL AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE ACTIONS OR INACTIONS OF ANY LENDER. THEFALLONGROUP.COM DOES NOT ENDORSE ANY PARTICULAR LENDER OR LOAN PRODUCT. YOU ARE UNDER NO OBLIGATION TO USE THE SERVICE, INITIATE CONTACT, OR REQUEST CREDIT WITH ANY OF THE LENDERS. THIS SERVICE IS NOT AVAILABLE IN ALL STATES. THE RESIDENTS OF ARKANSAS, NEW YORK, VERMONT AND WEST VIRGINIA WILL NOT BE ABLE TO USE THE SERVICE OF THE WEBSITE. SERVICE AVAILABILITY AND SCOPE ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE.
SUBJECT TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY, THEFALLONGROUP.COM WILL TRANSFER YOUR INFORMATION TO LENDERS IN OUR PROGRAM AND OTHER SERVICE PROVIDERS AND MARKETING COMPANIES WITH WHICH WE DO BUSINESS WHO MAY OR MAY NOT OFFER PAYDAY LOANS UP TO $1,000 AND ONLINE PERSONAL LOANS UP TO $35,000. THEFALLONGROUP.COM DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT COMPLETING AN ONLINE FORM WILL RESULT IN YOUR BEING MATCHED WITH A LENDER, BEING OFFERED A LOAN PRODUCT WITH SATISFACTORY RATES OR TERMS, OR A LOAN PRODUCT OF THE REQUESTED SUM OR DESIRABLE TERMS, OR RECEIVING ANY APPROVAL FROM A LENDER IN THE FIRST PLACE.
CREDIT CHECK: PARTICIPATING LENDERS MAY VERIFY YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER, DRIVER LICENSE NUMBER, NATIONAL ID, OR ANY OTHER STATE OR FEDERAL IDENTIFICATIONS AND REVIEW YOUR INFORMATION AGAINST NATIONAL DATABASES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO EQUIFAX, TRANSUNION, AND EXPERIAN, TO DETERMINE YOUR CREDIT WORTHINESS, CREDIT STANDING AND/OR CREDIT CAPACITY. BY SUBMITTING YOUR INFORMATION VIA OUR ONLINE FORM ON THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO ALLOW ANY AND ALL PARTICIPATING LENDERS TO VERIFY YOUR INFORMATION AND CHECK YOUR CREDIT.
NOT ALL THE LENDERS IN OUR NETWORK CAN PROVIDE UP TO $1,000 IN PAYDAY LOANS AND $35,000 IN ONLINE PERSONAL LOANS. THE LIMITS AND REGULATIONS VARY FROM STATE TO STATE. CASH TRANSFER TIMES AND TERMS MAY VARY FROM LENDER TO LENDER.
CONSUMER NOTICE: WE REMIND THAT PAYDAY LOANS AND ONLINE PERSONAL LOANS FOR SMALL DOLLAR AMOUNTS ARE NOT A LONG TERM FINANCIAL SOLUTION. THESE CREDIT OPTIONS IMPLY RELATIVELY HIGH INTEREST RATES AND BECOME A VERY COSTLY SOLUTION IF USED IMPROPERLY. CONSUMERS THAT SEEK FUNDS FOR LONGER TERMS OR DEBT RELIEF SHOULD CONSULT CREDIT OR FINANCIAL ADVISOR PRIOR TO MAKING CREDIT DECISIONS OF TAKING A SHORT TERM OR AN ONLINE PERSONAL LOAN FOR SMALL DOLLAR AMOUNT.
Theme by HermesThemes
Copyright © 2020 The Fallon Group - Online Loans. All Rights Reserved
